

# CHRISTINE PABLO

VISUAL DESIGNER
FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### PORTFOLIO

www.seepablo.com

#### **EMAIL**

christine.pablo@gmail.com

## PHONE

312.479.3154

#### SKILLS

#### / PROFICIENT

Photoshop Illustrator HTML CSS/SASS Powerpoint

#### / WORKING

InDesign JavaScript Node Git

#### / BASIC

MySQL MongoDB

#### / SOFT

Creativity
Problem Solving
Collaborative
Communication
Adapability

I'm a user-focused visual designer and front-end developer with a Flash motion background. With 10+ years working in small and large agency environments, I enjoy collaborating with others as well as working independently. My goal is to integrate technology with design to solve problems and provide a delightful user experience.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### FREELANCE FRONT END DEVELOPER / 2018 - present

Designed and built a mobile-first self-care website. Front-end design lead on a dog-sharing service website. Managed cryptocurrency web project.

#### FREELANCE VISUAL DESIGNER / 2013 - present

Redesigned and built, via CMS, websites for small businesses. One site saw increased membership by 80%. Batch designed and packaged online display ads. Designed and built email blasts using Constant Contact EMS. Created Powerpoint presentations for top PR agency and pharma clients.

## FLASH MOTION DESIGNER

# Razorfish, Chicago IL / 2008 - 2013

Animated and optimized online display ads according to media buy specs. Prepared and packaged ads for deployment. Collaborated with social media team in creating editorial content.

#### **DESIGNER**

## Wire Stone LLC, Chicago IL / 2006 - 2008

Collaborated with client and their vendors in creation of assets for use in product video launches, large format displays, and other various marketing materials. Responsible for management and handling of unreleased client product.

#### EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Certification / 2018 UCF Continuing Education, Orlando FL

Associate of Science, Digital Arts and Design / 2006
Full Sail University, Winter Park FL

Bachelor of Fine Arts, Fashion Design / 2000 Savannah College of Art and Design, Savannah GA